

Contact

+91 8946891025

bk769221@gmail.com

Sirohi, Rajasthan

Bhavesh Kumar

bhaveshkumar96

Bhavesh Kumar

Education

Full Stack Web Development

Masai School, Banglore May 2022 - Present

Civil Engineering

RTU Kota, Rajasthan Aug 2013- july 2017

Technical Skills

- JavaScript
- DSA
- React
- MongoDB
- HTML & CSS

Soft Skills

- Team Work
- Remote Work
- Netwoking

Interests

- Vollyball
- Movies

Certificates

- **NCC Barmer Training Certificate**
- Basic Web Development

BHAVESH KUMAR

Full Stack Web Developer

Professional Summary

Enthusiastic Full Stack Web Developer specialized in MERN stack. Keen interest in learning new things and working with dynamic teams. Practiced 400 hours of coding. Looking forward to an exciting opportunity and Development experience in a product-based company.

Projects

Shephora.Com





Shephora is an E-commerce website selling Beauty Products

Features

- Navigation bar & footer
- Sign-up & sign-in page
- Attractive landing page
- Cart page

Tech-stack

 JavaScript, HTML & CSS It was an Individual project build in 4 days

DNA INDIA NEWS (C)





Website is about daily news and updates

Features

- Navigation bar & footer
- News Categories pages
- Attractive landing page
- Detailed News page

Tech-stacks

- JavaScript, HTML & CSS
- News API

Area of Responsibility

• Make Navigation Bar, Footer part and side bar collaborative project build by team of 4 members

Professional Experience

Site Engineer - 1 Year (May 2021- May 2022)

JBC Architect & Associates, Pali

Site Engineer - Jan 2021 - June 2021

PM Jan Awas Yojana, Udaipur

HDM-Follow-up (Sep 2019 - March 2020)

Mangalam Info. Tech., Ahemedabad

Data Analyst (Semi - Government) - (Jan 2018 - Sep 2018)

Maharaja Ummed Singh Krishi Mandi, Sumerpur